imc2.com 2017-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Moroch Partners

Moroch Holdings, Inc. and its affiliates and subsidiaries (“Moroch,” “we,” or “us”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors of Moroch websites (each a “Site”). While you are visiting the Site, we may ask you (“you” or “your”) to provide information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”) for purposes of interacting with the Site or to allow you to submit additional information.

We will take measures so that the Personal Information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein. To further the protection of your Personal Information, we have adopted a set of information management guidelines (outlined below) to describe the Personal Information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties.

This Privacy Policy has been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy is subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Please see the Effective Date stated at the conclusion of this Policy.

### Type Of Information Collected

We collect only Personal Information that you submit to us, including but not limited to personal data (e.g., your name, mailing address, and email address), for example when you request further information. You are not obligated to provide us with this information, although it may be necessary in order to fulfill your request or allow you to submit additional information. Additionally, we may collect aggregate information regarding users of the Site. Aggregate information includes data regarding usage of the Site including traffic patterns, number of Site visits, use of particular services on the Site, etc. This information is NOT identifiable to individual Site users.

### Use Of Personal Information (subject To The Internal Policy Of Moroch)

We do not sell or otherwise disclose information about you, except as described here. We may share the information you provide with companies affiliated with Moroch. We also may share information provided by our Site visitors with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are required to use or disclose the information only as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event that we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use information you have provided through the Site in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.  
Additionally, we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with our business partners and other affiliated third parties (e.g., the number of users who have visited the Site on a specific day, etc.). Moroch may also match aggregated user information with third-party data and disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to potential advertisers, partners, and other third parties and for other lawful purposes.

It should be noted, however, that this Privacy Policy addresses only the use and dissemination of information that we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose any information to other parties, through other websites on the Internet linked to the Site, different policies may apply. Since Moroch does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies, if any, of those third parties, and Moroch shall not be responsible for the use or dissemination of your Personal Information by those third parties. Therefore, we encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information to others.

By submitting Personal Information, you grant permission to the Site for use consistent with this Privacy Policy. Consent will be assumed unless otherwise stated by you at the time of submission.

### Children’s Privacy

Moroch does not specifically collect information about children but is concerned about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, in accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such Personal Information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical. The Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of 13 without parental consent.

### Third-Party Hosting

Moroch contracts with one or more third parties to maintain and host the Site. Therefore, any information you submit, including Personal Information, shall be placed and stored on a computer server maintained by this third party. Your use of the Site and any provision of Personal Information you submit to the Site constitutes your acknowledgment that such information or content could pass through and may be stored in servers outside the control of Moroch. You agree that Moroch has no liability or responsibility for any such pass-through or storage of same.

### Effective Date and Changes

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 2015. Moroch reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time, and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the Site after our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes. You should periodically check this Privacy Policy for updates and/or changes.
